Family Blood is a horror, thriller film directed by Sonny Mallhi.
Ellie, a recovering drug addict, has just moved to a
new city with her two teenage children.
She has struggled to stay sober in the past and is determined to make it work this
time, finding a stable job and regularly attending her meetings.
Unfortunately, new friends, a new job, and the chance of a new
life, can’t keep Ellie from slipping once again.
Her life changes when she meets Christopher – a different kind of addict – which
forces her daughter and son to accept a new version of Ellie.
Ellie, played by Vinessa Shaw.
Christopher, played by James Ransone.
Kyle, played by Colin Ford.
Amy, played by Eloise Lushina.
Meegan, played by Ajiona Alexus.
Kristen, played by Carson Meyer.
Family Blood is a 2018 American horror film directed by Sonny
Mallhi and written by Nick Savvides and Mallhi.
It stars Vinessa Shaw, James Ransone, Colin Ford, Ajiona Alexus,
Carson Meyer, France Jean-Baptiste and Eloise Lushina.
Blumhouse Productions, Divide/Conquer and Gunpowder & Sky
released the film on May 4, 2018 via Netflix.
The film explores themes of vampire, addiction, drugs, family, psychotic.
The tone is dark and intense.